Special agent Fowler, please come in.
福勒探员 请进
What's private Daley doing here with that camera?
为什么列兵戴利会在那里摄像？
He will be making a record of today's session.
他将为今天的会话做记录
Soldier... too close.
士兵 太近了
Sorry I didn't dress for the occasion.
很抱歉我的穿着不合场合
Formality won't be any more necessary than usual, Bill.
与平时一样就好 比尔
But I do need to inform you that our higher-ups are on the war path.
但我不得不通知你 我们的上司已经做好了战争准备
They want answers regarding recent events.
他们得明白最近事件发生的原委
Perhaps we should begin with the demise of Optimus Prime.
或许我们应该从擎天柱的死亡开始
I thought we've straightened all this out.
我以为我们已经讨论过了！
Prime is alive and well.
擎天柱现在活得很好
That's difficult for our superiors to accept,
这对高层来说很难接受
without the benefit of seeing Optimus and the alleged imposter.
除非能看到擎天柱和他的仿冒品
Side by side? That didn't seem to be the wisest option at the time.
看到他们两个站在一起？目前看来是不行了
The sky jockeys were under direct orders to destroy any and all Autobots on sight.
空军接到直接命令 一旦发现任何汽车人 立即摧毁
We were in a heightened state of security.
我们现在在高度戒备状态
Let's consider the positives.
来说说好消息
We now possess greater intel regarding M.E.C.H..
现在我们掌握了关于机械党的更多情报
Particularly their leader, Silas.
尤其是他们的匪首 塞拉斯
the stage name of one Colonel Leland Bishop, ex-special tactics.
真名是莱兰・毕晓普 上校 前特种战术部队成员
The architect of project Damocles.
主导设计了达摩克利斯计划
Satellites in orbit firing laser beams at any target on Earth.
通过卫星激光束 攻击地球上的任意目标
Long since mothballed,
很早以前就废止了
and the primary reason for Bishop's discharge.
这也是毕晓普叛逃的主要原因
He had other wild ideas, which he practiced with even greater abandon once he went rogue.
叛逃之后 他更肆无忌惮地 重拾曾经放弃的其他疯狂计划
And still, no sign of his remains.
现在仍没有找到他的尸体
Of greater concern,
更令人担心的是
M.E.C.H. agents, like Silas, might also be special tactics.
塞拉斯的手下可能也是特战成员
As in, currently enlisted?
难道是现役人员？
One obvious motive for hiding their faces.
所以他们要把脸蒙上
I would urge a thorough investigation,
我想申请继续深入调查
and leave bigger threats to metal hands more capable than our own.
而我们的金属大手朋友在这方面要远远胜于我们
Because you've been allowed to operate at these deeply classified levels,
因为你被批准进行如此高度机密的任务
perhaps you could provide some background.
所以或许我们需要你提供背景资料
Our transforming visitors are autonomous, robotic organisms,
我们的变形朋友是有着自主意识的机械生命体
from the planet Cybertron. They were fighting a war.
来自塞博特恩星球 他们曾经历了一场战争
Foremost, over control of our world's supply of Energon,
核心问题 是为了我们的世界对于能量的控制权
the fuel and lifeblood of all Autobots and Decepticons alike.
也就是汽车人以及霸天虎的生命能量
Do you recall the period late in the war,
你还记得战争的末期吗？
when both sides began hiding their Energon spoils off-world?
双方都把找到的能量藏在外星球
Of course, it's the reason Energon deposits exist on planets such as this one.
当然记得 所以在这样的星球上会有能量矿
It is also the reason battles came to be waged on planets such as this one.
正是如此 这样的星球上才会有战争
These battles over Energon, and its dark counterpart, continue to this day.
这场争夺能量和黑暗能量的战争 延续至今
And you know this for certain?
你对这些确信吗？
I've seen more than enough to make me a believer.
我的所见不但使我信服
But I rely upon field reports from team Prime,
我还通过擎天柱的队伍获取战场情报
which I, in turn, share with you.
然后再共享给你
Skip ahead, if you would,
能跳过这些吗？
to the history of your involvement, Agent Fowler.
直接叙述你所参与的部分 福勒探员
As you know, I wasn't overjoyed with what I assumed was gonna be a bot-sitting assignment.
你也知道 我刚开始并不喜欢这项看管汽车人的工作
Prime!
擎天柱！
Wait. Don't tell me. He's out pancaking a mini-mall.
等等 别告诉我你们在办托儿所吗？
But its occupational hazards turned out to be surprisingly severe.
然而我发现这项工作的危险系数过于惊人
Bring the prod.
把能量棍拿来…
And, by now, the bots have saved my bacon more times than I can count.
另外汽车人也无数次挽救了我的生命
Of course, I've returned the favor a time or two...
当然 我也投桃报李 还了一些人情
Any time, fella. Ground floor's coming fast.
随叫随到 伙计 着地支援这就来
... sometimes exercising my authority...
有时需要利用下职权
The girl comes with me.
这女孩我带走
... sometimes relying upon quick thinking.
有时需要依靠敏捷的思维
We were just... calibrating the subsystems, and we, uh,
我们就是…校准了一下系统 我们还…
had a... surge.  But it's fine now.
有点小问题 但现在好了
How are you?
你那边好吗？
And I've made a few mistakes.
我也犯过一些错
Ah! Not again!
啊！又来这套！
Ah! Not this again!
啊 又是这套把戏！
If you would, Agent Fowler, provide a roll call.
福勒探员 能逐一介绍一下他们吗？
So, we'll know who's who in the event of another bot snaps?
要是碰巧遇上 我们好分清张三李四？
Something like that.
没错
Well, there's...
好吧那么…
Bulkhead.
隔板
Are you a car?
你是一辆车？
I bet you're a truck ... a monster truck!
我敢说你是卡车 是大脚车！
Do you like heavy metal? How much do you weigh?
你喜欢重金属音乐吗？你多重？
Ever use a wrecking ball for a punching bag?
用破碎锤打过沙包吗？
Look, Miko, before I became a warrior, I was a laborer
听着 神子 我在成为战士之前 是个工人
-- nstruction. I can build stuff. I can break stuff.
建筑工 我能造东西 也能拆东西
And that's it.
可别的都不会
Of course, big foot and I don't always see eye to eye.
当然我跟这个大块头并不很投缘
Don't use that phone. It's...
别用那个电话 它…
out of order.
坏了
He may not be the most agile bot...
他不是最敏捷的汽车人
Don't look down.
别往下看
And he's the first to admit he's no rocket scientist.
他也是最不可能成为科学家的一个
Come on, Doc. There's nothing up there to scan.
拜托 医生 没什么好检查的
Switch it back! I want to see the hoedown showdown!
把频道调回去 我想看完这整场节目
But his brute strength is invaluable.
但他的蛮力是无价之宝
Thankfully, the science angle is more than covered by Ratchet.
所幸救护车是技术领域的专家
The Doc can be a little... tightly wound.
医官他比较…严谨
Without my supervision?!
你们也想做到最好吧？
You want them to be right, don't you?
那就欣赏大师的手笔吧！
Control freak.
控制狂
But he brings his "A" game when the situation calls for it.
但当需要他战斗时也毫不含糊
It's all right.
没事了
I'm an emergency vehicle.
我是一辆救护车
Then there's Arcee.
还有阿尔茜
The motorcycle?
那辆摩托车？
Don't be fooled by the smaller footprint.
不要被那小巧的身材所迷惑
She leaves a mark.
她很厉害
Bumblebee's the team scout.
大黄蜂是队伍中的侦察兵
But the warrior-in-training seems pretty accomplished, if you ask me.
但要我说 这个还在培训中的战士比看上去要成熟
Arcee may be a bot of few words,
阿尔茜可以说是少言寡语了
but Bumblebee doesn't use any...
而大黄蜂更是完全不能说话…
... that we can understand.
…说了我们也听不懂
I-It wants us to get in.
它…想让我们上车
No, just me.
不 就我一个
How do you know that?
你怎知道的？
It said so.
它就是这么说的
Turns out it's with good reason.
这跟他的一段经历有关
During the war for Cybertron,
在塞博特恩的战争中
the poor kid got his voice box torn out by Megatron.
这个可怜的孩子被威震天损毁了发声器
So, the Autobots aren't quite the indestructible war machines we'd hoped.
所以汽车人并非如我们所想的那般坚不可摧
Don't misunderstand. They can take serious punishment.
不要误会 他们具有很强的抗击打能力
But they do have their... vulnerabilities.
但他们确实有弱点
Did you just scream like a little girl?
你刚刚像小女孩一样尖叫了吗？
No! Maybe...
没有 或许吧
This may not be the finish that we had planned,
这或许不是我们意料中的结局
but if this is indeed the end,
但如果真要在这里结束
if we are to become one with the Allspark...
如果我们要和火种源融为一体…
No. Cliffjumper's life signal
不！飞过山的生命信号…
just went offline.
刚刚消失了
If Cliff's gone, standing around here sulking won't bring him back.
站在这儿哭是不会让他复生的
We learned that the hard way when we lost Cliffjumper.
我们曾经在失去飞过山时悲痛地认识到了这一点
And, for the record, Cliffjumper was the last Autobot casualty?
根据你的报告 飞过山是上一个阵亡的汽车人？
I told you. The lifeless Autobot you have in storage isn't Prime.
我告诉过你 你缴获的那个无生命的汽车人不是擎天柱
It's a Knockoff!
那是个冒牌货
We have only your word to go on
我们只是听了你的一面之词
without any trace of Silas,
并没有发现塞拉斯的踪迹
or the alleged technology M.E.C.H. utilized to control said Knockoff.
也没有证据表明他掌握了复制和遥控技术
A clean scrub is M.E.C.H.'s M.O.
清除一切痕迹是机械党的处事方法
You and I both know it!
你和我都了解这点！
Your last debriefing indicated that Optimus Prime had joined the Decepticons.
你最后的报告中称擎天柱加入了霸天虎！
Not willfully! Prime had amnesia.
那不是他自愿的！擎天柱失忆了
I know I was clear on that.
我以为我已经说得很清楚了！
But you can see where outside observers might connect the dots to the recent attack on our base.
但你要明白我们的外部观察员 可以把这个与最近军事基地的遇袭联系起来
Bill, the five-stars have grown
比尔 五星上将们很担心
nervous that we've been placing our trust in beings who could so easily inflict harm
我们信任的这些生命体 一旦反目
if they chose to turn on us.
能轻而易举地伤害我们
That's why I've been asked to determine
因此我接到命令来审查你
whether I should bring you before a tribunal.
决定是否交付军事法庭
Tribunal? They could shut down our operation,
军事法庭？他们会停止整个行动！
put me in jail.
把我关进监狱！
General Bryce, Prime is no loose cannon.
布莱斯将军 擎天柱不是莽撞的人！
He's anything but.
他绝对不是！
The bots may be big, but they watch where they step.
汽车人虽然很巨大 但他们行动很谨慎
Heck, even the kids...
哪怕是孩子们…
Kids?
孩子们？
Ah... that's what we call our...
啊 哈哈 我们是这样称呼我们的…
"in-house support team".
…室内预备队的
I wasn't aware you were utilizing any of our resources other than yourself.
我不知道除了你以外
They're... not enlisted.
他们不是…现役军人
You've involved civilians in a classified operation?
你让平民涉入军事机密行动？
Highly accomplished civilians who contribute specialized expertise in...
他们是优秀的人才 在…
computer science... medicine... uh... communications.
计算机 医学 以及…沟通交流方面有杰出的贡献
I love breaking stuff!
我喜欢拆东西！
Twisted.
变态！
Bring the hurt!
把心脏带回来
Nerd alert.
书呆子又来了
Zombie!
僵尸！
Smackdown in outer space. That was cool.
是从外太空降临的 太厉害了…
So, they know how to take orders.
那么他们会服从命令吧
You... could... say that.
可以…这么说吧
Welcome to K.O. Drive-In, where every patty's a Knockout.
欢迎光临KO快餐厅 每个肉饼都顶呱呱
May I take your order?
您想要点什么？
But while they lack in military discipline,
但是他们打破常规思维去解决问题的方式
Nothing.
唉 没声音
Gee, imagine that.
天哪 谁想得到
The fourth dimension has lousy cellphone reception.
四维空间的手机信号这么差
Wait, guys, guys, guys. The phone... rang.
嘿 伙计们…电话响了
We're getting a signal.
说明有信号
Maybe the Autobots can't see or hear us because...
汽车人看不见也听不见我们 可能是因为…
we're moving at hyperspeed or something.
我们也许在做超高速运动
Their courage is to be admired.
他们勇气可嘉
Hold him still!
把他按住！
They've proven, time and again,
他们一次又一次的证明了
that they're willing to put their lives on the line for their country...
他们为了自己的国家
and their planet.
自己的星球甘愿牺牲
So, your civilians have made enemy contact.
因此你的平民队员与敌人有过接触
I never forget a face... even that of a human.
我对面孔过目不忘 人类的也算上
You double-cross anyone,
你要是敢骗人
mine is the face you'll never forget! Never!
我让你永远忘不了我这张脸 给我记住！
They've... pretty much seen it all.
基本上 他们什么都见识过了…
Miko, look away!
神子 别看！
- But... - Turn your head away!
- 但… - 把头扭过去！
Rest assured, the safety of these humans... of all humans...
但是请放心 汽车人重视这些人类――
remains the primary concern of the Autobots.
甚至是所有人类――的生命安全
They have no protective shell.
他们没有防护罩！
If they get underfoot, they will go... squish.
如果不小心被踩到 他们就…扁了
Then, for the time being, Ratchet,
那么从现在起 救护车
we must watch where we step.
我们必须走一步 看一步
And our colleagues wouldn't have it any other way.
并且我们的同伴也不会改变这个立场
I'm living a dream here in bots' "wanna".
这儿对我来说就像天堂一样
And I will not allow you or anyone else to shatter it!
你们谁都别想破坏我的美梦！
They've forged meaningful bonds with the bots.
他们同汽车人建立了深厚的羁绊
Where's Arcee?
阿尔茜呢？
Why don't you just marry her?!
你干脆跟她结婚好了
I'm right behind you.
我就在你后面
And they provide valuable assistance whenever
在我忙于做其他事时
I'm otherwise engaged in the field.
他们为汽车人提供了可贵的帮助
You've reached special Agent William Fowler.
这是威廉・福勒特工的电话号码
I'm currently on an intensive training retreat
我正在进行秘密强化训练
and unavailable until Tuesday.
周二之前不会回来
I hate talking to machines.
我讨厌跟机器说话
But their involvement was never intended to be
他们参与的所有行动
anything other than humanitarian...
都是经过人道主义考量的
to provide the Autobots with the means of better understanding life on our planet.
通过他们 汽车人对地球上的生命加深了了解
A scout should be silent but deadly.
侦察兵应该能杀人于无形
What?
怎么？
Maybe it needs one of these doohickeys.
可能还要装一个小东西
You're a motorcycle, Arcee.
你是摩托车 阿尔茜
Shouldn't you know how to build a motorcycle engine?
你难道不会制造摩托发动机吗？
You're a human, Jack. Can you build me a small intestine?
你还是人类呢 杰克 你能造出小肠来吗？
You want me to not only bridge you into a confined space
你们要传送的地方 不光是密闭空间
but one traveling at 90 miles per hour?!
而且移动速度每小时140多公里！
I can't even count the number of ways that can go wrong...
我根本无法想象可能出现的意外
mass displacement, trauma, twisted limbs, metal burn.
大面积错位损伤 四肢骨折 金属烧伤
Well, maybe not the last one.
呃 也许没有最后那种
Sadly, we haven't begun to take full advantage of their science.
不过 他们的很多科学技术我们都还没学到
I mean, I can pilot my v-tol without ever having to wear a flight suit.
比如 我可以不穿航空服驾驶垂直起降战机
What keeps your organs from exploding?
你的内脏不会爆炸吗？
A modification Ratchet performed on the cabin-pressure regulator.
救护车对机舱内的调压器做了改进
I like to be comfortable.
我…喜欢舒服一些
We... may be getting off track.
…有些跑题了
Please address why we haven't yet been served Megatron's steel head on a silver platter.
请你说明为什么威震天的项上人头还未被献上？
No!
不…
The leader of the Decepticons has nine lives, plain and simple.
霸天虎头目的生命力极其顽强…答案简单明了
Well, I'm staring right at him.
可我看见的确实是他
Good news is, Megatron isn't exactly staring back.
好消息是 威震天没有回应我的目光
It's not like we haven't tried.
我们并非没有尝试过
The sick part is,
糟糕的是
the moment we might have pulled it off, we needed him.
当我们能干掉他的时候 我们需要他
Megatron actually helped us save humanity.
威震天事实上帮助过我们拯救了全人类
Optimus, our past alliances... Autobot, Decepticon...
擎天柱 我们过去的阵营 什么汽车人 霸天虎
no longer matter... not while Unicron lives.
都去他的吧 眼下 宇宙大帝复活了
Elaborate.
请解释
We found ourselves facing an even greater threat than M.E.C.H. or the Decepticons.
我们遇到了一个比机械党和霸天虎更具威胁的敌人
Literally an enemy within...
就在地球内部 字面上的内部
Unicron. I know this is gonna sound crazy, but what if I told you
宇宙大帝…我知道这听起来很疯狂 不过我要是告诉你
our planet's core isn't made up of what science has led us to believe it is?
地球的核心跟科学理论的解释完全不同时
Agent Fowler, I'm sorry to say I'm forced to discontinue this debriefing until you undergo a full psychological evaluation.
福勒探员 看来我得中止这次会谈 让你先接受心理评估
Seriously?
你是认真的吗？
As a representative of the United States Government,
作为美国政府的代表
I believe that you may have lost your sanity.
我认为你心智不大正常
General Bryce, I assure you that I am quite sane.
布莱斯将军 我向你保证我神志清醒
It defies all logic, Bill. Dark Energon?
此事与逻辑完全相悖 比尔 黑暗能量？
Then you go on record saying that you believe in
然后又当着笔录员说
magical horses with horns on their heads.
你相信头上长角的魔马？
What?
什么？
Do you deny previously reporting that Megatron helped defeat a Unicorn?
你不是报告说 威震天协助打败了独角兽吗？
That's what you...
你以为…
Unicron! The ultimate evil!
宇宙―大帝！终极恶魔！
Permission to strike this from the record.
请划掉这一段
Granted. But consider yourself on notice.
批准 不过警告你注意言辞
You were saying. Megatron proved to be an ally.
你说过 威震天一度与我们联手
The circumstances were unique.
这种情况很罕见
Oddly, the 'con most likely to be of service is Starscream...
相反 霸天虎中最有可能为我们所用的是红蜘蛛
only be default...
这只是权宜之计
because he may despise his team more than he despises ours.
因为他对他自己的同伴的仇视 比对我们还深
No, master!
不 主人！
Starscream's loyalty to Megatron has always been questionable.
红蜘蛛在威震天面前一直三心二意
If he has truly split from the Decepticons,
如果他真的和霸天虎决裂
our prisoner's knowledge of their agendas could make him a valuable ally.
这个了解军情的俘虏 也许是个值得结交的盟友
Megatron tried to extinguish my Spark in cold blood!
威震天不念旧情 想把我干掉
Then all that replaced me with that traitorous wretch, Arachnid.
还有那个一心想取代我的混蛋毒蜘蛛
She abandoned me! Left me for scrap!
她竟然丢下我不管！让我自生自灭！
So why not rat them out?
所以 干嘛不过河拆桥呢？
But even after Megatron attempted to terminate him,
然而即便威震天一度试图处决他
Starscream still tried to win his master's faith.
红蜘蛛仍然试图赢得主人的欢心
Imagine Megatron's appreciation when I not only rescue him
威震天该对我刮目相看 我不光救了他
but deliver an Autobot.
还抓了个汽车人
I believe that would restore my stature quite nicely.
那样一来 我就可以重振雄风了
Starscream's insecurity is what makes him less predictable than Megatron.
由于缺乏安全感 红蜘蛛比威震天更难以捉摸
And in some ways, even more dangerous.
某种程度上 甚至更加危险…
I make the decisions here. I am in charge!
我说的话就是圣旨 这儿我说了算！
He really needs to figure out if it's Megatron's job he wants or Megatron's approval.
他真该分清楚自己到底是想要取代威震天 还是要在威震天面前得宠
I must, in turn, ask why successful termination of Starscream
我又要追问一下
has not been achieved.
为什么红蜘蛛还未被成功消灭？
Air superiority continues to provide the 'Cons with the upper hand.
空中优势一直使得虎子们占尽上风
though we manage to inflict the occasional setback.
个别时候 我们也能挫伤对方
But the fact remains...
但难以逆转劣势
Starscream has supplied valuable intel since he went rogue.
红蜘蛛落跑以后 为我们提供了宝贵的情报
Starscream: "I have obtained information regarding your leader.
我得到了关于你们领袖的情报
Bring medical kit."
带上医疗箱
Not to worry. The bots know better than to trust him implicitly.
不用担心 汽车人不会盲目地听信他
One step and your previous biomech is scrap.
再靠近一步 就把你的小器官变成废铁
Fortunately for us, despite his strategic brilliance,
幸运的是 尽管战略眼光独到
Starscream is his own worst enemy.
红蜘蛛最大的敌人就是他自己
What?
嗯 什么？
My T-cog!
呃 我的变形齿轮！
You're grounded?
你飞不起来了？
And he isn't the only one who's taken flight from Megatron.
他也不是唯一叛离威震天的人
The spider.
那只蜘蛛？
Airachnid, as sadistic as they come.
毒蜘蛛 生性残忍
And she and Arcee have quite a history.
她和阿尔茜有着很深的过节
I can't help but feel the next time
我总觉得
they lock horns, only one's gonna walk away.
下一次她们将战个你死我活
Unless Megatron gets to Airachnid first.
除非威震天先找到毒蜘蛛
So, the infighting among the Decepticon ranks continues.
所以说霸天虎的内斗一直不断？
And then some. Megatron can't seem to keep his inner circle holding hands.
不仅如此 威震天看似无法团结他的核心集团
And you don't think we could take advantage of the chaos?
你不认为我们能利用霸天虎的内斗吗
Motivate a Decepticon to join our cause?
说服霸天虎投诚？
There is one whom Prime seems to respect.
有一名霸天虎受到擎天柱的尊敬
While it is unlikely that any Decepticon will choose the path of good,
尽管霸天虎改邪归正的可能性不大
even they possess the potential for change.
但他们毕竟有改变命运的潜力
But having witnessed Dreadwing tear up a town,
但在目击骇翼夷平一座小镇后
I wouldn't hang my hopes on it.
我对他已不抱任何希望
So I must press the point...
我不得不说
if Optimus believes that even a Decepticon holds the potential for change,
既然擎天柱都相信霸天虎有投诚的潜质
why couldn't the reverse be true?
为什么汽车人就不会叛变呢？
No one truly knows what went on behind the Decepticon curtain
擎天柱在霸天虎阵营的那段时间里
while Optimus was off the grid?
谁知道发生了什么？
Not you, not the Autobots.
你不了解 汽车人也不了解
I'm 100% with Ratchet on this one.
关于这点 我百分之百的同意救护车所说的
Being a Decepticon is a choice, Agent Fowler.
是否成为霸天虎需要做出选择 福勒探员
one that I have a hard time believing Optimus would make at any point in his life.
我绝不相信擎天柱会在有生之年做出这样的决定
Orion Pax may not currently be an Autobot up here,
奥利安・派克斯也许现在不知道自己是汽车人
but I must believe he will never stop being one in here.
但我坚信在他的内心深处 绝不会放弃追逐理想
Against all odds, suffering amnesia,
面对艰难的逆境和失忆
Prime engineered his own escape to face down Megatron.
擎天柱仍然得以逃脱并且正面对抗威震天
But is Prime capable of change?
擎天柱会改变吗？
You know your problem, Optimus?
你知道你的问题吗 擎天柱？
For such a big, strong bot, you're soft.
你是个如此高大 如此强壮的汽车人 却如此…优柔寡断
You didn't pound Megatron into scrap when you had the chance!
你没有抓住机会把威震天砸成废铁！
Many chances, in fact!
错失了那么多良机！
You might as well use your drill to finish me.
你可以用钻头把我杀掉
What are you waiting for? Think of the glory?
你还等什么？这是莫大的荣耀
Seize the day. Optimus would.
机不可失 擎天柱会趁机动手的
No, he wouldn't.
不 他不会
So, tell me, Optimus, do you intend to take me alive
请告诉我擎天柱 你会放我一马吗？
or end this here and now?
或是就此了结恩怨
Prime has recently proven he's willing to go
擎天柱刚用实际行动证明
further than ever to protect humanity.
为了保护人类他不惜付出任何代价
Optimus Prime is a true patriot.
擎天柱是一个真正的爱国者
He and his team continue to risk their lives,
他和他的团队冒着生命危险
day in and day out,
日以继夜
asking absolutely nothing in return.
并且不求任何回报
If you don't survive, Optimus,
万一你牺牲了 擎天柱
I fear neither will this planet.
恐怕这星球也活不成了
Very well.
那好吧
The simple fact is,
简单明了地说
Prime doesn't have a bad circuit in his body.
擎天柱的身体里没有一块坏电路
Move it, gramps!
快走啊 死老头！
Agent Fowler, is that really necessary?
福勒探员 有这个必要吗？
As liaison to the Autobots,
作为跟汽车人的联系人
I strongly caution that
我极力警告你们
now would be the worst time to call Prime's dedication into question.
现在怀疑擎天柱的奉献精神 绝对不合时宜
We're on the verge of an even greater threat than we faced before.
我们可能要面临一个前所未有的威胁
The Decepticons are on the hunt for long-buried relics from Cybertron.
霸天虎们正在寻找来自塞博特恩的远古遗物
Preliminary intel suggests they could be sacred objects with mystical properties,
初步情报显示这些是拥有神秘力量的圣物
or weapons of mass destruction.
或是大规模杀伤性武器
Mystical?
神秘力量？
Uh, strike that, too!
啊 这一行也划掉！
The point I'm trying to make here is... Agh!
我的中心意思是 啊！
Hold on! Prime? I need an assist.
等一等！擎天柱？我需要帮助
Agent Fowler, have you uncovered M.E.C.H. agents?
福勒探员 你发现机械党成员了吗？
No. They're okay.
没有 不是他们
General Bryce here just needs to confirm the state of your health and welfare.
布莱斯将军想要了解你的健康状况
I am fine, General Bryce.
我很好 布莱斯将军
How are you?
你好吗？
I'm well, uh, soldier.
我很好 战士？
Bill... I believe I have everything I need to make a persuasive case
比尔 我想现在我能作一份有足够说服力的报告
that Optimus Prime is, indeed, alive and well.
证明擎天柱还健康地活着
And firmly on our side.
同时坚定不移地站在我们这边
We appreciate your support, sir.
我们很感激您的支持 长官
Dismissed.
准许离开！